<?xml version="1.0"?>
<b:Sources SelectedStyle="" xmlns:b="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/bibliography" xmlns="http://schemas.openxmlformats.org/officeDocument/2006/bibliography"><b:Source><b:Year>2020</b:Year><b:BIBTEX_Entry>book</b:BIBTEX_Entry><b:SourceType>Book</b:SourceType><b:Title>The gig economy : a critical introduction</b:Title><b:Publisher>Press, Polity Press</b:Publisher><b:Tag>Woodcock2020a</b:Tag><b:BIBTEX_Abstract>"All of a sudden, everybody's talking about the gig economy. From taxi drivers to pizza deliverers to the unemployed, we are all aware of the huge changes that it is driving in our lives as workers, consumers, and citizens. This is the first comprehensive overview of this highly topical subject. Drawing upon years of research, stories from gig workers, and a review of the key trends and debates, Jamie Woodcock and Mark Graham shed light on how the gig economy came to be, how it works and what it's like to work in it. THey show that, although it has facilitated innovative new services and created jobs for millions, it is not without cost. It allows businesses and govenments to generate value while passing significant risk and responsibility onto the workers that make it possible. This is not, however, an argument for turning back the clock. Instead, the authors outline four strategies that can produce a fairer platform economy that works for everyone." – Provided by publisher. Where did the gig economy come from? – How does the gig economy work? – What is it like to work in the gig economy? – How are workers reshaping the gig economy? – Conclusion: What's next for the gig economy? – Appendix: Draft convention on platform work.</b:BIBTEX_Abstract><b:URL>http://acdc2007.free.fr/woodcock2020.pdf</b:URL><b:Author><b:Author><b:NameList><b:Person><b:Last>Woodcock</b:Last><b:First>Jamie.</b:First></b:Person><b:Person><b:Last>Graham</b:Last><b:First>Mark.</b:First></b:Person></b:NameList></b:Author></b:Author><b:Pages>182</b:Pages><b:StandardNumber> ISBN: 9781509536375</b:StandardNumber></b:Source><b:Source><b:Year>2023</b:Year><b:BIBTEX_Entry>website</b:BIBTEX_Entry><b:SourceType>Misc</b:SourceType><b:Title>Q2 2021 shareholder letter</b:Title><b:Publisher>Upwork Inc.,</b:Publisher><b:Tag>UpworkInc2023a</b:Tag><b:URL>https://investors.upwork.com/static-files/820e9a32-eacc-45ec-8222-d453f555f040</b:URL><b:Author><b:Author><b:NameList><b:Person><b:Last>Upwork Inc</b:Last></b:Person></b:NameList></b:Author></b:Author><b:JournalName>Upwork Global, L. L. C.</b:JournalName><b:PublicationTitle>Q2 2021 shareholder letter</b:PublicationTitle></b:Source><b:Source><b:Year>2016</b:Year><b:Volume>27</b:Volume><b:BIBTEX_Entry>techreport</b:BIBTEX_Entry><b:SourceType>Report</b:SourceType><b:Title>What does the gig economy mean for workers?</b:Title><b:Tag>Donovan2016a</b:Tag><b:DOI>10.1080/10301763.2017.1377048</b:DOI><b:Author><b:Author><b:NameList><b:Person><b:Last>Donovan</b:Last><b:Middle>A.</b:Middle><b:First>Sarah</b:First></b:Person><b:Person><b:Last>Bradley</b:Last><b:Middle>H.</b:Middle><b:First>David</b:First></b:Person><b:Person><b:Last>Shimabukuro</b:Last><b:Middle>O.</b:Middle><b:First>Jon</b:First></b:Person></b:NameList></b:Author></b:Author><b:Pages>232–248</b:Pages><b:Month>July</b:Month><b:JournalName>Labour and a journal of the social, Industry: and economic relations of work</b:JournalName><b:StandardNumber> ISSN: 1030-1763</b:StandardNumber><b:ThesisType>Tech. rep.</b:ThesisType></b:Source><b:Source><b:Year>2019</b:Year><b:Volume>61</b:Volume><b:BIBTEX_Entry>article</b:BIBTEX_Entry><b:SourceType>JournalArticle</b:SourceType><b:Title>The organisation and experience of work in the gig economy</b:Title><b:Tag>Kaine2019a</b:Tag><b:BIBTEX_Abstract>The gig economy has captured public and policy interest and is growing as an area of academic inquiry, prompting debate about the future of work, labour regulation, and the impact of technology and job quality. This special issue provides a timely intervention into that debate with this article providing an introductory overview, positioning the articles within a comprehensive literature review of existing scholarship on the gig economy. These articles add to our understanding of the organisation and experience of work in the digitally enabled gig economy in a variety of national settings. They explore aspects such as job quality, forms of collectivity, identity development, and algorithmic management and control. This article also delineates avenues for further research regarding conditions for gig workers, the impact of gig work and information, technology and gig work.</b:BIBTEX_Abstract><b:DOI>10.1177/0022185619865480</b:DOI><b:Author><b:Author><b:NameList><b:Person><b:Last>Kaine</b:Last><b:First>Sarah</b:First></b:Person><b:Person><b:Last>Josserand</b:Last><b:First>Emmanuel</b:First></b:Person></b:NameList></b:Author></b:Author><b:Pages>479–501</b:Pages><b:Month>September</b:Month><b:JournalName>of Industrial Relations, Journal</b:JournalName><b:StandardNumber> ISSN: 0022-1856</b:StandardNumber></b:Source><b:Source><b:Year>2017</b:Year><b:Volume>28</b:Volume><b:BIBTEX_Entry>article</b:BIBTEX_Entry><b:SourceType>JournalArticle</b:SourceType><b:Title>Regulating work in the gig economy: what are the options?</b:Title><b:Tag>Stewart2017a</b:Tag><b:BIBTEX_Abstract>Paid work associated with digital platform businesses (in taxi, delivery, maintenance and other functions) embodies features which complicate the application of traditional labour regulations and employment standards. This article reviews the extent of this type of work in Australia, and its main characteristics. It then considers the applicability of existing employment regulations to these 'gig’ jobs, citing both Australian and international legislation and case law. There is considerable uncertainty regarding the scope of traditional regulations, minimum standards and remedies in the realm of irregular digitally mediated work. Regulators and policymakers should consider how to strengthen and expand the regulatory framework governing gig work. The article notes five major options in this regard: enforcement of existing laws; clarifying or expanding the definition of 'employment’; creating a new category of ‘independent worker’; creating rights for ‘workers’ rather than employees; and reconsidering the concept of an ‘employer’. We review the pros and cons of these approaches and urge regulators to be creative and ambitious in better protecting the minimum standards and conditions of workers in these situations.</b:BIBTEX_Abstract><b:DOI>10.1177/1035304617722461</b:DOI><b:Author><b:Author><b:NameList><b:Person><b:Last>Stewart</b:Last><b:First>Andrew</b:First></b:Person><b:Person><b:Last>Stanford</b:Last><b:First>Jim</b:First></b:Person></b:NameList></b:Author></b:Author><b:Pages>420–437</b:Pages><b:Month>September</b:Month><b:JournalName>Economic, The and Review, Labour Relations</b:JournalName><b:StandardNumber> ISSN: 1035-3046</b:StandardNumber></b:Source><b:Source><b:Department>freelancermap GmbH</b:Department><b:Year>2025</b:Year><b:BIBTEX_Entry>website</b:BIBTEX_Entry><b:SourceType>Misc</b:SourceType><b:Title>The freelancer study 2024</b:Title><b:Publisher>freelancermap GmbH</b:Publisher><b:Tag>Gmb2025a</b:Tag><b:BIBTEX_Abstract>The Freelancer Study is the result of an survey among freelancers and independent professionals. For the ninth time, the study analyzes working conditions, pricing and income trends, acquisition strategies, satisfaction levels, and both professional and structural challenges in the freelancing industry. A total of 3,571 freelancers and self-employed professionals were surveyed between January 13, 2025, and March 9, 2025. The results are further enriched by insights from freelancers, companies, and 16 industry and subject matter experts. We would like to take this opportunity to thank all participants, professionals, and contributors who have supported and made this study possible through their efforts.</b:BIBTEX_Abstract><b:URL>https://www.freelancermap.com/market-study</b:URL><b:Author><b:Author><b:NameList><b:Person><b:Last>freelancermap Gmb</b:Last></b:Person></b:NameList></b:Author></b:Author><b:JournalName>freelancermap GmbH</b:JournalName><b:PublicationTitle>The freelancer study 2024</b:PublicationTitle></b:Source><b:Source><b:Year>2020</b:Year><b:Volume>46</b:Volume><b:BIBTEX_Entry>article</b:BIBTEX_Entry><b:SourceType>JournalArticle</b:SourceType><b:Title>What do platforms do? Understanding the gig economy</b:Title><b:Tag>Vallas2020a</b:Tag><b:BIBTEX_Abstract>The rapid growth of the platform economy has provoked scholarly discussion of its consequences for the nature of work and employment. We identify four major themes in the literature on platform work and the underlying metaphors associated with each. Platforms are seen as entrepreneurial incubators, digital cages, accelerants of precarity, and chameleons adapting to their environments. Each of these devices has limitations, which leads us to introduce an alternative image of platforms: as permissive potentates that externalize responsibility and control over economic transactions while still exercising concentrated power. As a consequence, platforms represent a distinct type of governance mechanism, different from markets, hierarchies, or networks, and therefore pose a unique set of problems for regulators, workers, and their competitors in the conventional economy. Reflecting the instability of the platform structure, struggles over regulatory regimes are dynamic and difficult to predict, but they are sure to gain in prominence as the platform economy grows.</b:BIBTEX_Abstract><b:DOI>10.1146/annurev-soc-121919-054857</b:DOI><b:Author><b:Author><b:NameList><b:Person><b:Last>Vallas</b:Last><b:First>Steven</b:First></b:Person><b:Person><b:Last>Schor</b:Last><b:Middle>B.</b:Middle><b:First>Juliet</b:First></b:Person></b:NameList></b:Author></b:Author><b:Pages>273–294</b:Pages><b:Month>July</b:Month><b:JournalName>of Sociology, Annual Review</b:JournalName><b:StandardNumber> ISSN: 0360-0572</b:StandardNumber></b:Source><b:Source><b:Year>2020</b:Year><b:Volume>9</b:Volume><b:BIBTEX_Entry>book</b:BIBTEX_Entry><b:SourceType>Book</b:SourceType><b:Title>Gig economy, financial stability, efficiency in auto sector, opinion on budget</b:Title><b:Publisher>Publication, I. M. I. Kolkata</b:Publisher><b:Tag>Banik2020a</b:Tag><b:BIBTEX_Abstract>India has not witnessed any episode of extreme financial instability since the 1991 Balance of Payments (BoP) crisis, largely because of its insulated banking system with 90 per cent of bank liabilities being funded from retail depositors, sound macro-economic policies and cautious liberalisation, although spells of volatility have been observed in Indian financial markets following 2008 global financial crisis and 2013 taper tantrum. Periods of volatility have transformed the way fiscal and monetary policies work. Over the years, fiscal deficit reduction has freed up resources for the banking sector as the regulatory requirements have been progressively brought down. Fiscal policy has turned accommodative during periods of financial volatility and more recently the banking sector has been provided with capital as its provisioning requirements have increased after declaration of NPAs. In case of monetary policy, India formally adopted inflation targeting with price stability as the primary objective in 2016, after witnessing periods of high inflation. However, following the significant global volatility in recent times and the collapse of an NBFC behemoth in September 2019, the Indian central bank is now increasingly focused on maintaining financial stability. One such evidence was implicit when the Reserve Bank of India (RBI) refrained from raising interest rates in October 2018 policy to defend the Rupee against an overwhelming market consensus. In fact, RBI explicitly emphasized that the central bank was largely tolerant with the domestic exchange rate finding its market determined level and was concerned only to the extent that exchange rate depreciation feeds into headline inflation. The recent decline in growth numbers has further reinforced this consideration. In this article, we have focused on the banking sector and more recently NBFC sector, while outlining the recent policy changes which have been introduced to support the objective of financial stability.</b:BIBTEX_Abstract><b:Author><b:Author><b:NameList><b:Person><b:Last>Banik</b:Last><b:First>Arindam</b:First></b:Person><b:Person><b:Last>Chaudhuri</b:Last><b:First>Anoshua</b:First></b:Person><b:Person><b:Last>Suar</b:Last><b:First>Damodar</b:First></b:Person><b:Person><b:Last>Vij</b:Last><b:First>Madhu</b:First></b:Person><b:Person><b:Last>Sarkar</b:Last><b:Middle>Sekhar</b:Middle><b:First>Subhrangshu</b:First></b:Person><b:Person><b:Last>Mukherjee</b:Last><b:First>Paramita</b:First></b:Person><b:Person><b:Last>Basu</b:Last><b:First>Rituparna</b:First></b:Person><b:Person><b:Last>Chowdhury</b:Last><b:Middle>Roy</b:Middle><b:First>Sahana</b:First></b:Person><b:Person><b:Last>Chatterjee</b:Last><b:First>Rajashri</b:First></b:Person></b:NameList></b:Author><b:Editor><b:NameList><b:Person><b:Last>Mukherjee</b:Last><b:First>Paramita</b:First></b:Person><b:Person><b:Last>Basu</b:Last><b:First>Rituparna</b:First></b:Person><b:Person><b:Last>Chowdhury</b:Last><b:Middle>Roy</b:Middle><b:First>Sahana</b:First></b:Person></b:NameList></b:Editor></b:Author><b:StandardNumber> ISSN: 2321-9378</b:StandardNumber></b:Source><b:Source><b:Year>2019</b:Year><b:Volume>33</b:Volume><b:BIBTEX_Entry>article</b:BIBTEX_Entry><b:SourceType>JournalArticle</b:SourceType><b:Title>Good gig, bad gig: autonomy and algorithmic control in the global gig economy</b:Title><b:Tag>Wood2019a</b:Tag><b:BIBTEX_Abstract>&lt;p&gt;This article evaluates the job quality of work in the remote gig economy. Such work consists of the remote provision of a wide variety of digital services mediated by online labour platforms. Focusing on workers in Southeast Asia and Sub-Saharan Africa, the article draws on semi-structured interviews in six countries ( N = 107) and a cross-regional survey ( N = 679) to detail the manner in which remote gig work is shaped by platform-based algorithmic control. Despite varying country contexts and types of work, we show that algorithmic control is central to the operation of online labour platforms. Algorithmic management techniques tend to offer workers high levels of flexibility, autonomy, task variety and complexity. However, these mechanisms of control can also result in low pay, social isolation, working unsocial and irregular hours, overwork, sleep deprivation and exhaustion.&lt;/p&gt;</b:BIBTEX_Abstract><b:DOI>10.1177/0950017018785616</b:DOI><b:Author><b:Author><b:NameList><b:Person><b:Last>Wood</b:Last><b:Middle>J.</b:Middle><b:First>Alex</b:First></b:Person><b:Person><b:Last>Graham</b:Last><b:First>Mark</b:First></b:Person><b:Person><b:Last>Lehdonvirta</b:Last><b:First>Vili</b:First></b:Person><b:Person><b:Last>Hjorth</b:Last><b:First>Isis</b:First></b:Person></b:NameList></b:Author></b:Author><b:Pages>56–75</b:Pages><b:Month>February</b:Month><b:JournalName>Work, Employment and Society</b:JournalName><b:StandardNumber> ISSN: 0950-0170</b:StandardNumber></b:Source><b:Source><b:Year>2019</b:Year><b:BIBTEX_Entry>book</b:BIBTEX_Entry><b:SourceType>Book</b:SourceType><b:Title>Will the gig economy prevail?</b:Title><b:Publisher>Press, Polity</b:Publisher><b:Tag>Crouch2019a</b:Tag><b:BIBTEX_Abstract>"In this book, Colin Crouch takes a step back and questions the logic of the 'gig economy'. He shows how the idea of an employee - a stable status that involves a bundle of rights - has, despite many changes and threats, shown a curious persistence. It is for this individual that Crouch proposes an agenda for a realistic future of secure work" – Provided by publisher. The rise of precarious work – Ambiguities of the employment contract – The rise, fall and persistence of standard employment – The changing shape of precariousness – A new approach to employment security.</b:BIBTEX_Abstract><b:Author><b:Author><b:NameList><b:Person><b:Last>Crouch</b:Last><b:First>Colin.</b:First></b:Person></b:NameList></b:Author></b:Author><b:Pages>144</b:Pages><b:Month>June</b:Month><b:StandardNumber> ISBN: 9781509532469</b:StandardNumber></b:Source><b:Source><b:Year>2023</b:Year><b:BIBTEX_Entry>website</b:BIBTEX_Entry><b:SourceType>InternetSite</b:SourceType><b:Title>Gig economy statistics and key takeaways for 2024</b:Title><b:Tag>Kempton2023a</b:Tag><b:BIBTEX_Abstract>Rather than primarily relying on traditional 9-to-5 in-office employment, today many businesses and individuals are embracing the gig economy. Gig work involves short-term contracts and freelance work, which can fall into many categories, including but not limited to asset-sharing services, transportation, household tasks, and skilled, professional services. Whether you're an individual looking for work in the gig economy or a business leader interested in engaging independent talent, learn about how the gig economy has evolved, along with relevant statistics and trends in freelancing and gig work.</b:BIBTEX_Abstract><b:URL>https://www.upwork.com/resources/gig-economy-statistics</b:URL><b:Author><b:Author><b:NameList><b:Person><b:Last>Kempton</b:Last><b:First>Beth</b:First></b:Person></b:NameList></b:Author></b:Author><b:Month>October</b:Month><b:JournalName>Upwork Global, L. L. C.</b:JournalName><b:PublicationTitle>Gig economy statistics and key takeaways for 2024</b:PublicationTitle><b:RefOrder>16</b:RefOrder><b:Guid>{B20C5956-35B0-4319-A79C-2899303EE581}</b:Guid><b:YearAccessed>2024</b:YearAccessed><b:MonthAccessed>10</b:MonthAccessed><b:DayAccessed>17</b:DayAccessed><b:InternetSiteTitle>upwork.com</b:InternetSiteTitle></b:Source><b:Source><b:Year>2023</b:Year><b:BIBTEX_Entry>website</b:BIBTEX_Entry><b:SourceType>InternetSite</b:SourceType><b:Title>104 essential freelance stats 2024 [facts and trends].</b:Title><b:Tag>Todorov2023a</b:Tag><b:URL>https://thrivemyway.com/freelance-stats/</b:URL><b:Author><b:Author><b:NameList><b:Person><b:Last>Todorov</b:Last><b:Middle>G.</b:Middle><b:First>A.</b:First></b:Person></b:NameList></b:Author></b:Author><b:Month>May</b:Month><b:JournalName>Way, Thrive My</b:JournalName><b:PublicationTitle>104 essential freelance stats 2024 [facts and trends].</b:PublicationTitle><b:Guid>{E79A3E79-C152-4A0E-BFDD-B5D5C242EDC3}</b:Guid><b:YearAccessed>2024</b:YearAccessed><b:MonthAccessed>10</b:MonthAccessed><b:DayAccessed>17</b:DayAccessed><b:RefOrder>17</b:RefOrder><b:InternetSiteTitle>Thrive My Way</b:InternetSiteTitle></b:Source><b:Source><b:Year>2025</b:Year><b:BIBTEX_Entry>website</b:BIBTEX_Entry><b:SourceType>InternetSite</b:SourceType><b:Title>40+ incredible upwork statistics 2024 (revenue facts).</b:Title><b:Tag>Steven2025a</b:Tag><b:URL>https://khrisdigital.com/upwork-statistics/</b:URL><b:Author><b:Author><b:NameList><b:Person><b:Last>Steven</b:Last><b:First>K.</b:First></b:Person></b:NameList></b:Author></b:Author><b:Month>January</b:Month><b:JournalName>blog, KhrisDigital Marketing L. L. C.</b:JournalName><b:PublicationTitle>40+ incredible upwork statistics 2024 (revenue facts).</b:PublicationTitle><b:Guid>{802E8134-D63B-45B1-BDD5-EE9C4DB0BD8D}</b:Guid><b:YearAccessed>2025</b:YearAccessed><b:MonthAccessed>1</b:MonthAccessed><b:DayAccessed>26</b:DayAccessed><b:RefOrder>17</b:RefOrder><b:InternetSiteTitle>KhrisDigital</b:InternetSiteTitle></b:Source><b:Source><b:Year>2023</b:Year><b:BIBTEX_Entry>website</b:BIBTEX_Entry><b:SourceType>InternetSite</b:SourceType><b:Title>80+ upwork statistics in 2023: revenue, users and more</b:Title><b:Tag>Beckman2023a</b:Tag><b:URL>https://techreport.com/statistics/upwork-statistics/</b:URL><b:Author><b:Author><b:NameList><b:Person><b:Last>Beckman</b:Last><b:First>J.</b:First></b:Person></b:NameList></b:Author></b:Author><b:Month>October</b:Month><b:JournalName>TechReport</b:JournalName><b:PublicationTitle>80+ upwork statistics in 2023: revenue, users and more</b:PublicationTitle><b:Guid>{69C950CE-50FE-499A-B33E-CD9D7C61913C}</b:Guid><b:YearAccessed>2025</b:YearAccessed><b:MonthAccessed>1</b:MonthAccessed><b:DayAccessed>26</b:DayAccessed><b:RefOrder>17</b:RefOrder><b:InternetSiteTitle>Tech Report</b:InternetSiteTitle></b:Source><b:Source><b:Year>2023</b:Year><b:BIBTEX_Entry>website</b:BIBTEX_Entry><b:SourceType>DocumentFromInternetSite</b:SourceType><b:Title>How many people use upwork in 2023? (user &amp; revenue stats)</b:Title><b:Tag>Wise2023a</b:Tag><b:URL>https://earthweb.com/upwork-users/</b:URL><b:Author><b:Author><b:NameList><b:Person><b:Last>Wise</b:Last><b:First>J.</b:First></b:Person></b:NameList></b:Author></b:Author><b:Month>June</b:Month><b:JournalName>EarthWeb</b:JournalName><b:PublicationTitle>How many people use upwork in 2023? (user &amp; revenue stats)</b:PublicationTitle><b:RefOrder>13</b:RefOrder><b:Guid>{1AE50AA3-2DE2-497F-9556-EBB70A0ECDB2}</b:Guid><b:YearAccessed>2026</b:YearAccessed><b:MonthAccessed>02</b:MonthAccessed><b:DayAccessed>02</b:DayAccessed><b:InternetSiteTitle>Earth Web</b:InternetSiteTitle></b:Source><b:Source><b:Year>2023</b:Year><b:BIBTEX_Entry>website</b:BIBTEX_Entry><b:SourceType>InternetSite</b:SourceType><b:Title>Q1 2023 shareholder letter</b:Title><b:Publisher>Upwork Inc.,</b:Publisher><b:Tag>UpworkInc2023b</b:Tag><b:URL>https://investors.upwork.com/static-files/02975692-9913-4671-9c20-96528dd88634</b:URL><b:Author><b:Author><b:NameList><b:Person><b:Last>Upwork Inc</b:Last></b:Person></b:NameList></b:Author></b:Author><b:JournalName>Upwork Global, L. L. C.</b:JournalName><b:PublicationTitle>Q1 2023 shareholder letter</b:PublicationTitle><b:RefOrder>12</b:RefOrder><b:Guid>{F438F9BE-3167-4324-A3C9-B48D6482D593}</b:Guid><b:InternetSiteTitle>upwork.com</b:InternetSiteTitle><b:YearAccessed>2024</b:YearAccessed><b:MonthAccessed>10</b:MonthAccessed><b:DayAccessed>17</b:DayAccessed></b:Source><b:Source><b:Year>2020</b:Year><b:BIBTEX_Entry>website</b:BIBTEX_Entry><b:SourceType>DocumentFromInternetSite</b:SourceType><b:Title>Upwork review: all you need to know</b:Title><b:Tag>Clennett2020a</b:Tag><b:URL>https://wise.com/au/blog/upwork-review</b:URL><b:Author><b:Author><b:NameList><b:Person><b:Last>Clennett</b:Last><b:First>Samuel</b:First></b:Person></b:NameList></b:Author></b:Author><b:Month>September</b:Month><b:JournalName>Wise</b:JournalName><b:PublicationTitle>Upwork review: all you need to know</b:PublicationTitle><b:RefOrder>6</b:RefOrder><b:Guid>{78913FF9-94E8-4670-8416-D621A04AB0F5}</b:Guid><b:InternetSiteTitle>Wise</b:InternetSiteTitle><b:YearAccessed>2024</b:YearAccessed><b:MonthAccessed>10</b:MonthAccessed><b:DayAccessed>17</b:DayAccessed></b:Source><b:Source><b:Year>2024</b:Year><b:BIBTEX_Entry>website</b:BIBTEX_Entry><b:SourceType>InternetSite</b:SourceType><b:Title>Upwork review: does it meet our expectations in 2024?</b:Title><b:Tag>Melidoniotis2024a</b:Tag><b:URL>https://www.websiteplanet.com/freelance-websites/upwork/</b:URL><b:Author><b:Author><b:NameList><b:Person><b:Last>Melidoniotis</b:Last><b:First>Alexandros</b:First></b:Person></b:NameList></b:Author></b:Author><b:Month>August</b:Month><b:JournalName>Planet, Website</b:JournalName><b:PublicationTitle>Upwork review: does it meet our expectations in 2024?</b:PublicationTitle><b:RefOrder>5</b:RefOrder><b:Guid>{C2106A4E-11E9-4047-858D-2149367C6692}</b:Guid><b:InternetSiteTitle>Website Planet</b:InternetSiteTitle><b:YearAccessed>2024</b:YearAccessed><b:MonthAccessed>10</b:MonthAccessed><b:DayAccessed>17</b:DayAccessed></b:Source><b:Source><b:Year>2016</b:Year><b:BIBTEX_Entry>website</b:BIBTEX_Entry><b:SourceType>InternetSite</b:SourceType><b:Title>Why you should never use upwork, ever.</b:Title><b:Tag>Paterson2016a</b:Tag><b:URL>https://hackernoon.com/why-you-should-never-use-upwork-ever-5c62848bdf46</b:URL><b:Author><b:Author><b:NameList><b:Person><b:Last>Paterson</b:Last><b:Middle>Paterson</b:Middle><b:First>Allababidi</b:First></b:Person></b:NameList></b:Author></b:Author><b:Month>October</b:Month><b:JournalName>HackerNoon</b:JournalName><b:PublicationTitle>Why you should never use upwork, ever.</b:PublicationTitle><b:RefOrder>2</b:RefOrder><b:Guid>{1417B5F9-7745-4223-8BF6-0D21774C11D4}</b:Guid><b:InternetSiteTitle>Hacker Noon</b:InternetSiteTitle><b:YearAccessed>2024</b:YearAccessed><b:MonthAccessed>10</b:MonthAccessed><b:DayAccessed>17</b:DayAccessed></b:Source><b:Source><b:Year>2024</b:Year><b:BIBTEX_Entry>website</b:BIBTEX_Entry><b:SourceType>InternetSite</b:SourceType><b:Title>Workers on the gig economy: 2022 statistics</b:Title><b:Tag>Buffett2024a</b:Tag><b:URL>https://zety.com/blog/workers-on-gig-economy</b:URL><b:Author><b:Author><b:NameList><b:Person><b:Last>Buffett</b:Last><b:First>J.</b:First></b:Person></b:NameList></b:Author></b:Author><b:Month>June</b:Month><b:JournalName>Zety</b:JournalName><b:PublicationTitle>Workers on the gig economy: 2022 statistics</b:PublicationTitle><b:Guid>{7E22DDC7-43A4-4D26-9087-85FD5B9F62C0}</b:Guid><b:YearAccessed>2024</b:YearAccessed><b:MonthAccessed>10</b:MonthAccessed><b:DayAccessed>17</b:DayAccessed><b:RefOrder>10</b:RefOrder><b:InternetSiteTitle>Zety Blog</b:InternetSiteTitle></b:Source></b:Sources>
